const triviaItems = [
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "Blinky, Pinky, Inky and Clyde are characters from which classic video game?",
    correct_answer: "Pac-Man",
    incorrect_answers: ["Gauntlet", "Space Invaders", "Street Fighter"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "Which of these is NOT a main playable character in &quot;Grand Theft Auto V&quot;?",
    correct_answer: "Lamar",
    incorrect_answers: ["Trevor", "Michael", "Franklin"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "What does Solid Snake use to hide himself with?",
    correct_answer: "Cardboard Box",
    incorrect_answers: ["Cloaking Device", "Metal Crate", "Cardboard cut-out"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "In Minecraft, which two items must be combined to craft a torch?",
    correct_answer: "Stick and Coal",
    incorrect_answers: ["Stick and Fire", "Wood and Coal", "Wood and Fire"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Who created the &quot;Metal Gear&quot; Series?",
    correct_answer: "Hideo Kojima",
    incorrect_answers: ["Hiroshi Yamauchi", "Shigeru Miyamoto", "Gunpei Yokoi"],
  },

  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "Lanky, Funky, and Chunky are all characters featured in which series owned by Nintendo?",
    correct_answer: "Donkey Kong",
    incorrect_answers: ["Mario", "Kirby", "Zelda"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "What&#039;s the best selling video game to date?",
    correct_answer: "Minecraft",
    incorrect_answers: ["Wii Sports", "Tetris", "Super Mario Bros"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "The most graphically violent game to precede the creation of the ESRB (Entertainment Software Rating Board) was...",
    correct_answer: "Mortal Kombat",
    incorrect_answers: ["Duke Nukem", "Resident Evil", "Doom"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "In Kingdom Hearts, how many members does Organization XIII have in total?",
    correct_answer: "14",
    incorrect_answers: ["10", "13", "12"],
  },
  {
    category: "Entertainment: Video Games",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Who is the main character in &quot;The Stanley Parable&quot;?",
    correct_answer: "Stanley",
    incorrect_answers: ["The Adventure Line", "The Narrator", "The Boss"],
  },
];

export default triviaItems;
